doggies.com 2018-07-20

# Doggies.com Privacy Policy

Doggies.com is an internet website where people can share information about their dogs, including pictures and videos, with other dog owners, guardians and lovers. All subscribers, visitors and participants in or to doggies.com are covered by our Ironclad Privacy Policy.

**What information do we collect from you?**

When you register to participate in doggies.com and at other times, we collect your name, email address and zip or postal code. If you register your dog, we collect information about your dog including its name, age, breed, gender, activities, etc.

In order to maximize the value of the website to its users we collect aggregate information about visits to the site (such as which pages are visited) and we collect information about   
visitors’ computers (such as such as browser type, browser language, and IP address). This information is never shared with anyone, period.

**How do we use the information we collect from you?**

We will never sell, rent, barter or otherwise share your name, email address or other personal identifying information to any outside party.

We may use information in the following ways:  
For the purposes for which you specifically provided the information including, for example, to enable us to process, validate and verify subscriptions.  
To send you e-mail notifications about our new or existing products and services, special offers, or to otherwise contact you.  
To enhance existing features or develop new features, products and services.  
To provide advertisers and other third parties with aggregate information about our user base and usage patterns.  
To allow us to personalize the content and advertising that you and others see based on personal characteristics or preferences.

We may use third party network advertisers to deliver ads to you on our behalf. These network advertisers and service providers may be supplied with or have access to your personally identifiable information solely for the purpose of providing these services to us or on our behalf.

Except as specifically set forth in this Ironclad Privacy Policy, we will not share your personally identifiable information outside of doggies.com and its affiliates unless you specifically agree to having your personally identifiable information shared with a company that is not affiliated with us.

We will use information you enter about your dog only to display it on the web site or on our affiliated web site, breeders.net; it will never be sold, rented, bartered or otherwise shared to any outside party. Since the website is accessible by anyone with an internet connection and a web browser, any information, pictures and videos you post can be copied by any other internet user. Although we discourage abusive copying, the opportunity for it is an inherent part of the internet. You should never give us information, pictures or videos that you do not now or ever want someone else to have access to.

**Legal requirements**

You acknowledge and agree that doggies.com may disclose your personal information and the contents of your account if required to do so by law or in a good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order, or to protect the rights and property of doggies.com, its affiliates or the public.

**Removal of your information**

You may at anytime edit any information or remove your dog and personal accounts entirely. We require only that you provide and maintain a valid and current email address while you have an account so we may contact you.

We reserve the right to transfer your submitted information in the event of a transfer of ownership of doggies.com, such as acquisition by or merger with another company. In such an event, we will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

**Cookies**

We send "cookies" to your computer and use such cookies as described here. A cookie is a piece of data that identifies you as a unique user. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service and make the service easier to use for our members. We do this by storing user preferences in cookies and by tracking user trends - for example, we use cookies to allow you to automatically log in to the service after the first user session. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Be aware, however, that some parts of doggies.com may not function properly if you refuse cookies. There is a consensus among internet security experts that cookies do not represent a security or privacy risk to internet users.  
**  
External links**

Doggies.com may contain links to other web sites. These other sites maintain their own policies regarding cookies and the collection and use of personal information.

**Security**

We use industry standard security measures to protect your information so that it is not made available to unauthorized parties. If you have any questions regarding which measures and techniques we use, feel free to contact us at http://www.doggies.com/contact.php.

**Modification**

From time to time, we may update the Ironclad Privacy Policy and we will post a notice of significant changes on the web site. You should visit this page periodically to review any such changes to the Ironclad Privacy Policy.

**Consent**

By using doggies.com, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as outlined in this Ironclad Privacy Policy.

**Questions?**

If you have any questions or concerns about this Ironclad Privacy Policy, you may contact us at http://www.doggies.com/contact.php.
